# **Zed Poirier**

## **SUMMARY**

My skillset focuses on creating engaging, immersive experiences by using iterative design principles, low-detail 3D modelling, and efficient scripting techniques for quick prototyping.

• VR & Mobile Development

• Technical Art Focus

• Rapid Gameplay Prototyping

• Bilingual (English & French)

## **SKILLS**

**Languages & Engines:** C#, Unity, Python, Godot, HLSL, HTML, CSS **3D Art Software:** Blender, Maya, 3DS MAX, Substance Painter

Multimedia: Adobe Suite, OBS, Google Docs

**Production:** Jira, Trello, GitHub, SVN, Google Drive

# **EXPERIENCE**

**3D Digital Artist - April 2019 to Present** 

VARLab - Kitchener, ON

- Customized demos to meet the needs of international industry end clients
- Developed and integrated digital assets for virtual reality training simulations
- Researched techniques to improve efficiency of asset creation and demo performance

**Game Master -** August 2018 to January 2019

MirageVR - Kitchener, ON

- Documented system bugs and potential performance improvements to the dev team
- Troubleshot technical errors during setup and mid-game to ensure a smooth experience

Customer Service Guru - Sept 2016 to April 2018

**Shopify Inc.** - Kitchener, ON

- Solved clients' technical issues over phones, chats, and emails
- Coordinated with multiple teams simultaneously to speed up resolutions

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Game Design Diploma**

#### **Broadcast Television Diploma**

- Sept 2018 to present
- Conestoga College, Kitchener, ON
- Sept 2013 to April 2014
- · Conestoga College, Kitchener, ON

#### **OTHER QUALITIES**

• Gamemaster in roleplaying games such as D&D, Savage Worlds, and Blades in the Dark